hello everybody and welcome to the 9th
大家好，欢迎 来到9号
TV basics tutorial video in this video
本 视频中的电视基础教程视频
we're gonna be talking about a couple of
我们会谈论 几个
things one is the screen manager will
屏幕管理员将会做的事情之一
just barely touch on that before moving
在移动之前几乎没有碰到那个
into it the next video as well as the
进入它的下一个视频以及
Builder which will be the primary focus
生成器将成为主要 焦点
of this this video so once you start
这个视频， 所以一旦你 开始
building a large enough application
构建足够大的应用程序
whatever the framework you're using is
无论你使用的框架是什么
you're gonna find that you're gonna need
你会发现你 会需要的
a fundamental thing and that's to move
一个基本的东西，那就是 移动
between windows basically or be able to
窗口之间基本上还是能够
change the screen so you need to be able
改变屏幕， 所以你需要能够
to have the user you know say click on
让你知道 的用户 说 点击
settings and settings menu pops up or
设置和设置菜单弹出或
you know navigate between I don't know
你知道我不知道 之间的导航
various types of Windows and this is
各种类型的 Windows和这 是
actually traditionally kind of difficult
实际上传统上有点困难
especially unlike tkinter if you recall
尤其不像tkinter，如果你记得
in pygame the way that we do it is just
在 pygame中，我们这样做的方式就是这样
by cleaning the entire slate and then
通过清洁整个石板然后
redrawing on it with tkinter we have
我们用tkinter重新绘制它
basically all of the windows in the
基本上所有 的窗口都在
background and then we load the one that
背景，然后我们加载一个
we're most interested in at the moment
我们目前最感兴趣的是
make that on top basically how keavy
基本上 ，这 基本上是 如何keavy
works but luckily TV wrote that code for
作品，但幸运的是电视写了代码
us on like tkinter which we had to kind
我们喜欢tkinter，我们必须善良
of write the code so anyways let's go
编写代码这样反正我们走吧
ahead and talk about those two things
提前并谈论 这两件事情
but mainly we're going to talk in this
但主要是我们要谈这个
tutorial video about the Builder so the
关于Builder的教程视频 如此
idea of builder is so with these key v
这些关键 诉诉的建设者的想法是如此
files we saw that basically we have to
我们看到的文件基本上是我们必须的
have that key v file at least besides
至少还有 那个关键的 v文件
app this word is needs to be the word of
应用这个词是需要成为的话
the key v file and i don't really like
关键的v文件 ， 我不太 喜欢
that i think that's kind of messy and at
我认为那是一种混乱和在
least is especially here where we're
特别是 我们最不在乎的地方
changing like say versions and stuff
像说的版本和东西改变
like that um it gets kind of tedious and
就像那样，它会变得 乏味和尴尬
annoying that it's not really explicit
讨厌它不是很明确
it's almost like an implied kind of
它几乎就像一种隐含的
thing where it just needs to be
它只是需要的东西
basically like the root of app needs to
基本上就像应用程序需要的根源一样
be the word it's just kind of messy I
是这个词，它只是一种混乱的 我
don't really like it so anyways uh there
不管怎么说，不要那么喜欢它
is another methodology to bringing in
是另一种引入方法
key v files and that's with the Builder
关键v文件 ，这是与 生成器
so I'm gonna delete basically all of
所以我 会 删除基本上所有的
this code here really I guess we'll
这里的代码真的我想我们会的
leave that and we'll leave that but
离开这一点，我们会离开，但
basically all of this code now you might
基本上所有这些代码现在你可能
want to leave it here because we're
想要留在这里， 因为 我们是
going to come
即将到来
- this little widget we're going to use
- 我们将使用这个小部件
it again in a little bit but I'm trying
它再次在一点点 ，但 我正在努力
to make sure we pair everything down to
确保 我们将所有东西都配对
the most basic values so when we add new
最基本的价值，所以当我们添加 新的
things you understand where the
你明白在哪里的东西
fundamentals of those new things so I'm
这些新事物的基础， 所以我是
going to delete everything basically up
要 删除一切基本上达到
to here and we'll leave the main app now
到这里 ，我们 现在 就离开主应用程序
the next thing that we're going to do is
接下来 我们要做的是
instead of in fact what we can't what
而不是实际上我们不能做什么
I'll do now we'll leave it sorry so the
我现在要做， 我们会离开 对不起， 所以
first thing we want is builder now we
我们现在想要的第一件事就是建造者
have to import that that's not something
必须导入那不是什么东西
that just like naturally comes with key
就像自然而然地带着钥匙一样
or naturally is imported with say app of
或自然是与说的应用程序进口
key V and so what we're going to say is
关键V，所以我们 要说的是
from key V dot Lang imports builder and
从关键V点郎进口建设者和
then we're just we just need a reference
那么我们只是需要一个参考
builder and so we're gonna say basically
建设者，所以我们 会基本上说
like this you would say for example
像这样你会说例如
we'll say presentation since the kini
我们会说 基尼 以来的 演讲
files really are just your presentation
文件确实只是演示
I like to use the word presentation
我喜欢用这个词表达
equals builder daunt load underscore
等于builder daunt 加载下划线
file and the file we want to load is
文件和我们要加载的文件是
just the name of that KB file in our
只是在我们的KB文件的名称
case I've called mine main dot TV that's
这种情况我称为我的主要点电视
this file here so now that will blow
这个文件在这里，所以现在会吹
that file in and it really doesn't
该文件，它真的没有
matter what the name of this class is
不管 这个班的名字是 什么
really so that's basically it the only
真的，这基本上 是唯一的
other change you would really need to
你真的需要其他变化
make is you would take presentation and
make是你 会采取 演示文稿和
have it return presentation now there's
现在有它返回演示文稿
really nothing to this application we
真的没有这个应用程序我们
don't really have anything here at the
在这里没有任何东西
moment so we're gonna have to add
所以我们必须补充
something here so presentation has
这里介绍了一些东西
something to present but I did just want
有些东西要呈现， 但我只是想要
to cover builder before we hop into the
在我们跳进去之前覆盖建筑商
next next thing which will be the actual
接下来的事情将是实际的
screen manager but to use that we're
屏幕管理器，但要使用我们
also going to use builder and that
也将使用建设者和那个
should help me moving forward with these
应该能帮我 做 这些 前进
tutorials a lot easier because I kept
教程更容易，因为 我保持
forgetting to change this name and this
忘记改变这个名字和这个
name and it was quite annoying so
名字，这是非常烦人的
anyways that's it for this one real
反正就是它这一个真正的
quick simple tutorial with Builder
使用 Builder快速简单的教程
before I guess suppose before we move on
在我们猜测之前， 我们继续前进
I will just say that builder you can
我 只会说建造者你可以
also do instead of load file give you
也做而不是加载文件给你
something like load string
像 加载字符串
and you could load the string like so so
你可以加载像这样因此字符串
you could have your triple quotes here
你可以在这里得到你的三重引号
triple quotes here and then you could
三重引号在这里，然后你可以
basically copy and paste your key D file
基本上复制并粘贴你的密钥 D文件
right in there so like this and that's
在那里就像 这样，那就是了
completely acceptable that would work as
完全可以接受的 工作
well with key V I'm not going to really
以及关键V我不会 真的
do that I don't feel like that's you
这样做，我不觉得 这就是你
might as well just write it in Python if
不妨把它写在 Python中
you're gonna do that
你会这样做的
uh so anyway I'm not really gonna do
呃所以无论如何 我 真的不会做
that I like the load file better I think
我认为我更喜欢加载文件
that's pretty pretty good idea so
这非常好主意
anyways that's what we will do moving
无论如何，这是我们将要做的事情
forward pretty simple tutorial but if
转发 非常简单的教程，但如果
you do have any questions or comments
你有任何问题或意见
please feel free to leave them below
请随时给 他们 留下 下方
otherwise as always thanks for watching
否则一如既往感谢收看
thanks for all the support subscriptions
感谢 所有支持 订阅
and until next time
直到下一次